&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们专门讨论布尔值。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's talk about == specifically with Booleans.
这是另一个真正邪恶的角落案件，你不应该做的。
This is another one of those really evil corner cases that you shouldn't do.
这是您在代码中经常做的事情，而且
This is something that you do a lot in code, and
这是你绝对不应该做的事情。
it's something you should definitely not do.
你这样做是因为你习惯于用其他语言来做这件事，而且
It's something you do because you're used to doing this in other languages, and
在这里，它会给你带来麻烦的。
here, it's gonna get you into trouble.
好的，如果你想检查是否允许
Okay, if you wanna check if you want to allow
数组的布尔强制为真。
the Boolean coercion of an array to be true.
换句话说，你想说它真实的构造。
In other words, you wanna say its truthy sort of construct.
这是我可以接受的事情。
That is something that I'm okay with.
有些人对此并不满意。
Some people are not okay with that.
但假设你暂时这么做了。
But let's say that you do for the moment.
有一种方法可以做到这一点，那就是做一个if语句。
There's one way of doing it, which is just just to do an if statement.
允许if语句调用数组上的to布尔操作，
Allow the if statement to invoke the to Boolean operation on the array, which,
在本例中，是一个查找，表明数组不在表上，所以，
in this case, is a lookup that says the array is not on the table, so,
因此，这是真的。
therefore, it's true.
这是布尔强制的完全理性隐含。
That's a perfectly rational implicit to Boolean coercion.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：但是如果你试图用它变得更聪明和更狡猾，你会说，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: But if you try to get more clever and tricky with it and say,
好吧，如果是真的，
well, if it's truthy,
那么也许我应该做的是做一个与真相等的双倍。
then maybe what I ought to do is do a double equals with true.
好吧，现在突然之间它不起作用了。
Well, now all of a sudden it doesn't work.
顺便说一句，它也不适用于三重等于。
And by the way, it wouldn't work with triple equals either.
因为将布尔值与数组进行比较将经历一大堆这样的比较
Cuz the comparison with a Boolean to an array is gonna go through a bunch of those
拐角案件，我们已经确认了，我们正准备重新确认。
corner cases, which we've already identified and we're about to re-identify.
而且它也会等于假。
And also it's gonna be equal to false.
所以现在你会得到你直觉上所期望的东西的倒退。
So now you're gonna get the backwards of what you would intuitively expect.
你认为这件事是真的，它不是双倍等于真的，但是
You think this thing is truthy, it is not double equal to true, but
它是双倍等于假的。
it is double equal to false.
毫无疑问，这是一个难题。
And there's no question that this is a gotcha.
但在我解释这个问题之前，我的答案是永远不要重复，
But before I even explain the gotcha, my answer to this is don't ever do a double,
或者即使在这种情况下，如果你能避免三倍。
or even in that case, if you can avoid triple.
但绝对不要用true做双等号或用false做双等号。
But definitely, never do a double equals with true or a double equals with false.
因为没有需要用true或
Because there's no scenario where you need to do a double equals with true or
当您只需隐式执行to Boolean时，double等于false。
double equals with false when you could just do the to Boolean implicitly.
没有比这更好的情况了。
There's no case where that or that is better.
有一大堆情况更糟，就像这个，好吗？
And there's a bunch of cases where it's worse, like this one, okay?
因此，让我们解释一下=true如何失败，而=false是如何工作的。
So let's explain how the == true fails but the == false works.
同样的步骤，同样的算法。
Same steps, same algorithm.
我们从最上面的开始。
We start with the top one.
当然如果车间的学生，我们只是做一个布尔值就可以了。
Of course if workshop students, we just do a to Boolean on it.
第4行，我们检查它的布尔值，然后
Line 4, we check for the Boolean on it, and
如果匹配得很好，在本例中是匹配的，所以我们运行核心分支。
if it matches great, in this case it does, so we run that core branch.
但是，当我们试图将其与真相等时，会发生什么呢？
But what happens when we're trying to double equal it with true?
嗯，我们有一个非原始的，需要变成原始的，所以
Well, we have a non-primitive which need to became primitive, so
它变成空字符串。
it becomes empty string.
我们有一个空字符串和一个true。
We have an empty string and a true.
这些不是相同的类型，所以它们都需要成为数字。
These are not the same type, so they need to both become numbers.
其中一个变成0，应该是NaN，另一个变成1。
One of them becomes 0, which should have been NaN, the other one becomes 1.
这两个数字肯定不相等，所以我们不运行那个代码分支。
And those two numbers are definitely not equal, so we don't run that code branch.
在另一个代码分支中，我们做了完全相同的事情。
In the other code branch we do the exact same thing.
我们从车间学生开始=假。
We start off with workshop students = false.
我们得到一个字符串=false，它变成0而不是0，并且
We get to a string = false, which becomes a 0 compared to a 0, and
那些0等于真。
those 0s are equal to true.
这是一个无稽之谈的结果，这是一个无稽之谈。
That's a nonsensical outcome to what was a nonsensical construct.
您不需要将等于值加倍为true，或者
You don't need to double equals to true, or
Double等于false，则允许隐式发生to Boolean。
double equals to false, allow the to Boolean to happen implicitly.
所以再一次
So yet again,
我想说的是，隐含有时比显性好得多。
what I'm saying is that implicit is sometimes much better than explicit.
在这种情况下，隐式没有明白，显式有。
In this case, the implicit doesn't have the gotcha and the explicit does.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：这个问题可能太宽泛，太笼统，但在其他情况下
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: This is maybe too broad a question, too generic, but in other cases
在那里你会走得更远，而不是跑IF车间的学生。
where you would go a step further and rather than running if workshop students.
你会检查所有的车间学生是否都有方法，
You would check if and then method all workshop students,
检查.length的存在以确保它是字符串或
checking the presence of .length to make sure it's a string or
数组，或者您正在检查其他类型特定的。
an array, or you're checking other type specific.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以这个构造的场景是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So the scenario of this construct is
我只想知道它是否设置好了。
I only wanna know whether it's set or not.
我知道它既可以是未设置的，也可以是
And I know that it can either be unset or
它可以设置为一个数组，这就是这个场景的心理构造。
it can be set to an array, that was the mental construct of this scenario.
所以这在其余的周围代码中是很明显的，或者
So that would have been obvious by the rest of the surrounding code or
至少希望周围代码的其余部分是显而易见的。
at least hopefully obvious from the rest of the surrounding code.
如果我们不知道，如果我们知道它可以被取消，或者它可以被设置
If we didn't know that, if we knew that it could be unset, or it could be set and
它可以设置为各种不同的东西，可能是一个数组，也可能是一个对象，
it could be set to a variety of different things, maybe an array, maybe an object,
也许是一根绳子。
maybe a string.
然后我们会想要做一些更深层次的检查，而不仅仅是to boolean
Then we would wanna do some sort of deeper checking than just the to Boolean
胁迫。
coercion.
这可能是检查它是否实际设置的第一步，并且
That might be the first step to check that it is actually set, and
那么下一个检查就是检查关于它的身份的一些东西。
then the next check is to check something about its identity.
你可以通过不同的方式来检查它。
And there's various ways that you could check it.
如果合适的话，可以使用某种类型的运算符。
You could use a type of operator, if that was appropriate.
你可以做你所指的事，
You could do what you're referring to,
这就是所谓的鸭子类型，检查是否有一个方法在它上面，
which is called duck typing, check to see if a method is on it,
您可以执行array.isarray这样的实际实用程序来检查它是否在数组中。
you could do an actual utility like array.isarray to check if it's in array.
如果你有很多其他的事情，你可能会想要做
There's a variety of other things that you might wanna do if you
特别想知道这是一个数组。
cared to specifically know it was an array.
但我这里的设置是我们已经知道它是一个数组，
But the setup I have here is that we would already know it's an array,
因为我们已经看到了第1行。
cuz we already see line 1.
它既可以被设置，也可以是一个数组，
It can either be set or it can be an array,
它不可能是介于两者之间的任何东西。
and it can't be anything else in between.
这说得通吗？
Does that make sense?
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：是的，我想我的问题是如果你通常会建议
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, and I guess my question is if you would typically advise
反对把它像鸭子一样打到第三行的支票上吗？
against packing it like duck typing into line 3 into that check?
试图将两者结合起来。
Trying to combine both.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：不，我不是这个意思。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: No, that's not what I'm saying.
我的意思是如果出于某种原因我不能限制
What I'm saying is I would do those if for some reason I couldn't restrict
我自己知道它不是一个未设置就是一个数组。
myself to know that it's either an unset or an array.
我更喜欢较小的表面积和较少的必要检查。
I would prefer a smaller surface area with fewer necessary checks.
我更喜欢设计这个代码，这样它就不会那么多态了。
I would prefer to design this code so that it's not so polymorphic.
它要么是完全未设置的，要么是一个数组。
It's either unset entirely or it's an array.
但是如果由于某种原因我不能以这种方式设计我的代码，
But if for some reason I couldn't design my code in that way,
然后，我会将这些额外的检查放入if语句中。
then I would put those extra checks into the if statement.
这有帮助吗？
Does that help?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的，那很好。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, that's great.
凯尔·辛普森：好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay.